<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Thirty Days Of Wellness</string>
    <string name="day_1">Day 1</string>
    <string name="day_1_title">Drink plenty of water throughout the day.</string>
    <string name="day_1_msg">Staying hydrated is essential for good health.</string>
    <string name="day_2">Day 2</string>
    <string name="day_2_title">Get enough sleep each night. </string>
    <string name="day_2_msg">Aim for 7–9 hours of sleep per night to feel your best.</string>
    <string name="day_3">Day 3</string>
    <string name="day_3_title">Eat a balanced diet with plenty of fruits and vegetables.</string>
    <string name="day_3_msg">A healthy diet can help you feel your best.</string>
    <string name="day_4">Day 4</string>
    <string name="day_4_title">Exercise regularly to keep your body healthy and strong.</string>
    <string name="day_4_msg">Regular exercise can improve your mood and reduce stress.</string>
    <string name="day_5">Day 5</string>
    <string name="day_5_title">Practice mindfulness and meditation to reduce stress and anxiety.</string>
    <string name="day_5_msg">Mindfulness can help you stay calm and focused.</string>
    <string name="day_6">Day 6</string>
    <string name="day_6_title">Take breaks throughout the day to stretch and move your body.</string>
    <string name="day_6_msg">Sitting for long periods can be harmful to your health.</string>
    <string name="day_7">Day 7</string>
    <string name="day_7_title">Spend time in nature to improve your mood and mental health.</string>
    <string name="day_7_msg">Nature has a calming effect on the mind and body.</string>
    <string name="day_8">Day 8</string>
    <string name="day_8_title">Connect with friends and family regularly to maintain social connections.</string>
    <string name="day_8_msg">Social connections are important for good mental health.</string>
    <string name="day_9">Day 9</string>
    <string name="day_9_title">Practice gratitude by writing down things you\'re thankful for each day.</string>
    <string name="day_9_msg">Gratitude can improve your mood and outlook on life.</string>
    <string name="day_10">Day 10</string>
    <string name="day_10_title">Set goals for yourself and work towards achieving them.</string>
    <string name="day_10_msg">Goals can give you a sense of purpose and direction in life.</string>
    <string name="day_11">Day 11</string>
    <string name="day_11_title">Take time each day to do something you enjoy.</string>
    <string name="day_11_msg">Doing things you love can improve your mood and overall well-being.</string>
    <string name="day_12">Day 12</string>
    <string name="day_12_title">Learn a new skill or hobby to keep your mind active.</string>
    <string name="day_12_msg">Learning new things can keep your brain healthy and engaged.</string>
    <string name="day_13">Day 13</string>
    <string name="day_13_title">Get outside and soak up some sunshine each day.</string>
    <string name="day_13_msg">Sunlight is important for good mental health.</string>
    <string name="day_14">Day 14</string>
    <string name="day_14_title">Limit your intake of processed foods and sugar.</string>
    <string name="day_14_msg">A healthy diet is key to good physical and mental health.</string>
    <string name="day_15">Day 15</string>
    <string name="day_15_title">Take care of your skin by wearing sunscreen and moisturising regularly.</string>
    <string name="day_15_msg">Skin health is important for overall well-being.</string>
    <string name="day_16">Day 16</string>
    <string name="day_16_title">Practice good hygiene habits like washing your hands frequently.</string>
    <string name="day_16_msg">Good hygiene can prevent illness and disease.</string>
    <string name="day_17">Day 17</string>
    <string name="day_17_title">Take care of your mental health by seeking help when needed.</string>
    <string name="day_17_msg">Mental health is just as important as physical health.</string>
    <string name="day_18">Day 18</string>
    <string name="day_18_title">Practice self-care by taking time for yourself each day.</string>
    <string name="day_18_msg">Self-care can help you feel refreshed and rejuvenated.</string>
    <string name="day_19">Day 19</string>
    <string name="day_19_title">Laugh often and surround yourself with positive people.</string>
    <string name="day_19_msg">Laughter is good for the soul!</string>
    <string name="day_20">Day 20</string>
    <string name="day_20_title">Listen to music or podcasts that inspire you or make you happy.</string>
    <string name="day_20_msg">Music has a powerful effect on mood.</string>
    <string name="day_21">Day 21</string>
    <string name="day_21_title">Keep your living space clean and organised to reduce stress.</string>
    <string name="day_21_msg">A cluttered space can lead to a cluttered mind.</string>
    <string name="day_22">Day 22</string>
    <string name="day_22_title">Take breaks from technology throughout the day to reduce screen time.</string>
    <string name="day_22_msg">Too much screen time can be harmful to your health.</string>
    <string name="day_23">Day 23</string>
    <string name="day_23_title">Read books or articles that interest you to keep your mind engaged.</string>
    <string name="day_23_msg">Reading is great for mental stimulation.</string>
    <string name="day_24">Day 24</string>
    <string name="day_24_title">Volunteer in your community to give back and feel good about yourself.</string>
    <string name="day_24_msg">Helping others is good for the soul!</string>
    <string name="day_25">Day 25</string>
    <string name="day_25_title">Spend time with animals to improve your mood and mental health.</string>
    <string name="day_25_msg">Animals have a calming effect on the mind and body.</string>
    <string name="day_26">Day 26</string>
    <string name="day_26_title">Practice deep breathing exercises to reduce stress and anxiety.</string>
    <string name="day_26_msg">Deep breathing can help you stay calm in stressful situations.</string>
    <string name="day_27">Day 27</string>
    <string name="day_27_title">Take care of your teeth by brushing and flossing regularly.</string>
    <string name="day_27_msg">Oral health is important for overall well-being.</string>
    <string name="day_28">Day 28</string>
    <string name="day_28_title">Get regular check-ups with your doctor to maintain good health.</string>
    <string name="day_28_msg">Regular check-ups are key to preventing illness and disease.</string>
    <string name="day_29">Day 29</string>
    <string name="day_29_title">Practice forgiveness by letting go of grudges or negative feelings towards others.</string>
    <string name="day_29_msg">Forgiveness is important for good mental health.</string>
    <string name="day_30">Day 30</string>
    <string name="day_30_title">Practice gratitude.</string>
    <string name="day_30_msg">Practice gratitude each day - this could be when you wake up, before bed, or during your lunch break at work.</string>
    <string name="expand_button_content_description">See more or less information about a wellness tip.</string>
    <string name="read_more">Read more...</string>
</resources>